Finding Aid for the John Egerton Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Generations (1983)
  - Tapes, Box 1
    - Row 1
      - Anita Ledford and Mary Helen Ledford Casey, 7/20/78 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Herb and Hazel Ledford, 8/3/78 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Carl and Gerry Ledford, 8/3/78 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - James Ledford, 8/3/78, and David & Kathy Ledford, 8/4/78, Helen & Henry Pope, 8/18/78, and Jerry & Brenda Ledford, 8/18/78 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Lucille L. Smith, 8/17/78 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Dorothy Jackson, 8/17/78. and Gary Hammon, 9/3/78 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - C.B. Ledford, 8/4/78; C.B. and Addie Ledford, 8/17/78; Becky & Richard Eversman, 9/3/78; C.B. and Addie Ledford, 9/3/78 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Billy Jack Ledford & family, 9/4/78; Tillie Ledford King, 9/4/78 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Row 2
      - Sally & Jerry Watkins, 9/13/78; C.B. and Addie Ledford, 9/15/78 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      - Eddie Ledford & family, 9/13/78; Steve Ledford, 9/13/78 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - Emily L. Lawrence and family, 9/14/78; C.B. and Addie Ledford, 9/15/78 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 9/15/78 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - Jane Ledford Shelton and Ronald, 9/26/78; C.B. and Addie Ledford, 10/4/78 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      - Martha Nolan, 10/4/78; Polly & Bob Hawkins, 10/4/78 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      - C.B. Ledford, 10/11/78; Eloise Ledford Beatty, 10/6/78 (Box 54, Folder 25)
      - Sarah Ledford, Kim Allen, 10/19/78; Nancy & Larry Allen, 10/19/78 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      - Nancy & Larry Allen (continued), 10/19/78; Charlie Bob Ledford, 10/20/78 (Box 54, Folder 27)
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 10/20/78; Richard Ledford, Judy Ledford, 10/20/78 (Box 54, Folder 28)
      - Judy Ledford (continued), 10/20/78; Arletta Bourne, 10/29/78; Eloise Beatty, 10/29/78 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      - Eloise Beatty, 10/29/78; Alice Fields, 11/8/78; Polly & Bob Hawkins, 11/15/78 (Box 54, Folder 30)
      - C.B and Addie Ledford, 11/16/78; David Smith, 11/16/78 (Box 54, Folder 31)
      - David Gastineau, 12/17/78; Gwen & Russell Gastineau, 12/18/78; Richard & Adrienne Gastineau, Rebecca Gastineau, 12/18/78 (Box 54, Folder 32)
      - C.B. Ledford (Side 1), 12/18/78; Addie Ledford (Side 2), 12/18/78 (Box 54, Folder 33)
      - Carole & Paul Starnes, 12/18/78 (Box 54, Folder 34)
      - Michael Ledford, 7/24/79; C.B. and Addie Ledford, 7/24/79 (Box 54, Folder 35)
      - Sue Ledford Rudd and C.B. and Addie Ledford, 8/25/79 (Box 54, Folder 36)
- Generations (1983)
  - Tapes, Box 2
    - Row 1
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 10/17/79; Addie Ledford, 11/13/79; C.B. Ledford, 11/13/79 (Box 55, Folder 37)
      - C.B.Ledford, 11/13/79; C.B. and Addie Ledford, 2/3/80 (Box 55, Folder 38)
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 3/5/80 (Box 55, Folder 39)
        Taped Interviews with C.B. and Addie Ledford by Polly Hawkins
      - & (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - C.B. Ledford, 7/7/76; C.B. Ledford, 7/7/76 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - & (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Addie Ledford, 7/7/76; C.B. and Addie Ledford, 7/7/76 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - & (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - C.B. Ledford, 7/26/76 and 6/15/77 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - & (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - C.B. and Addie Ledford, 6/15/77; C.B. and Addie Ledford, 6/15/77 (Box 55, Folder 8)
        Generations segment, National Public Radio’s Morning Edition with Bob Edwards, 10/13/83
        Interview with John Egerton by Studs Terkel, 11/2/83
        Interview with John Egerton on WEKY, Richmond, Kentucky (n.d.)
        Video Tape-Homecoming, 1983
        Video Tape-University Journal-Interview with John Egerton, 2/28/89
        See Box 89 for Oversized Photos from Generations
  - Nashville! (Text to Company Morrisey’s Photographs, 1984)-Research and Background Materials-Research Note (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Nashville! -Correspondence-Incoming (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Nashville! -Publication Materials-Contract (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Radnor Lake: Nashville’s Walden-1984-Manuscript (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Radnor Lake: Nashville’s Walden-Planning and Outlines (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Radnor Lake: Nashville’s Walden-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Radnor Lake: Nashville’s Walden-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Radnor Lake: Nashville’s Walden-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Radnor Lake: Nashville’s Walden-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Radnor Lake: Nashville’s Walden-Review (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Chain Prisons (The Progressive, 1984)-Research and Background Materials-Articles and Notes (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Chain Prisons-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - The Bottom Line (1985)-Manuscript (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Tennessee: A Homecoming (1985)-Manuscript (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Tennessee: A Homecoming-Planning and Outlines (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Tennessee: A Homecoming-Research and Background Materials-Interviews and Photos (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Tennessee: A Homecoming-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Tennessee: A Homecoming-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Appalachian Writing (Appalachian Heritage, Fall, 1985)-Manuscript (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - The W.O. Smith Community Music School (Video Script, 1986)-Manuscript (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - The W.O. Smith Community Music School- Background and Research Materials Interviews (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - The W.O. Smith Community Music School-Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes and Photos (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - The W.O. Smith Community Music School-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray (The Progressive, Nov., 1986) Manuscript (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray-Manuscript-Typescript and Proofs (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray-Planning and Outlines (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray-Research and Background Materials-Research Notes and Taped Interview with James Earl Ray (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 56, Folder 31)
- Southern Food - Edited Proofs
  - Introduction and Essay (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Eating Out and Eating Out for Breakfast (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Eating Out for Lunch, Eating Out Family Style, Eating Out for Dinner (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Eating Out in Louisiana, Eating Out by the Waters, Eating Out on the Barbecue Circuit, Eating Out All Over the South (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Eating In: Southern Food at Home, Accompaniments (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Eating In: Main Dishes, Side Dishes (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Eating In: Sweets, Conclusion (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Appreciation, Bibliography, Index of Recipes (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Marginalia (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Southern Food (1987)
  - Manuscript in Typescript
    - Introduction and Essay (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Eating Out and Eating Out for Breakfast (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Eating Out for Lunch (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Eating Out Family Style (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Eating Out for Dinner (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Eating Out in Louisiana (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Eating Out by the Waters (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Eating Out on the Barbecue Circuit (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Eating Out All Over the South and Roster of Restaurants (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Eating In: Accompaniments (Incomplete) (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Eating In: Beverages (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Eating In: Breads (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Eating In: Main Dishes (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Eating In: Side Dishes (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Eating In: Sweets (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Appreciation (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Bibliography (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Marginalia (Rowledge-Trillin) (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Marginalia (Schweid-Biggerstaff) (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Marginalia (Sokolov-Hitton) (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Southern Food (1987)
  - Edited Typescript
    - Introduction and Essay (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Eating In: Introduction, Accompaniments (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Eating In: Beverages (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Eating In: Breads (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Eating In: Main Dishes (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Eating In: Side Dishes (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Eating In: Sweets (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Eating Out: Introduction (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Appreciation (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Bibliography (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Roster of Restaurants (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Marginalia (Powledge-Trillin) (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Marginalia (Schweid-Biggerstaff) (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Marginalia (Sokolov-Hitton) (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Southern Food (1987)
  - Edited Typescript
    - Introduction and Essay (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Eating Out, Eating Out for Breakfast (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Eating Out for Lunch (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Eating Out Family Style (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Eating Out for Dinner (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Eating out in Louisiana (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Eating Out by the Waters (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Eating Out on the Barbecue Circuit (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Eating Out All Over the South (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Eating In: Introduction and Accompaniments (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Eating In: Beverages (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Eating In: Breads (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Eating In: Main Dishes (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Eating In: Side Dishes (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Eating In: Sweets (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Conclusion (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Bibliography (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Index (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Eating Out in Louisiana, Margin Notes by Richard Collin (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Southern Food (1987)
  - Edited Typescript
    - Introduction and Essay (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Eating Out, Eating Out for Breakfast (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Eating Out for Lunch, Eating Out Family Style (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Eating Out for Dinner, Eating Out in Louisiana (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Eating Out for Dinner, Eating Out on the Barbecue Circuit (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Eating out All Over the South, Roster of Restaurants (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Eating In: Introduction, Accompaniments (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Eating In: Beverages, Breads (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Eating In: Main Dishes (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Eating In: Side Dishes, Sweets (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Appreciation, Bibliography (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Marginalia (Powledge-Trillin) (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Marginalia (Schweid-Biggerstaff) 14, Marginalia (Sokolov-Hitton) (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Index; Index of Recipes (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Southern Food (1987)
  - Uncorrected Proof Copy (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript-Pp.1-88 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript-Pp. 89-184 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript-Pp.185-312 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript-Pp. 313-408 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Research and Background Materials-Photographs (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Research and Background Materials-Photographs (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Research and Background Materials-Photographs (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence-Incoming (Box 62, Folder 12)
    See Box 89 (Oversized Box) for Southern Food Proofs
  - Southern Food (1987)-Two videotapes-CBS Nightwatch, 7/6/87 and Southern Cookin’ (4 Parts) (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Southern Food (1987)-Three audiotapes-Bob Edwards, NPR, 6/22/87; Beattie, KY, 6/22/92; “Meat and Three”, All Things Considered, 3/9/95 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - South (1987)-Manuscript (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - South-Typescript of manuscript (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - South-Planning and Outlines (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - South-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - South-Publication Materials (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - South-Reviews (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Dishes and Beverages of the Old South by Martha McCullough-Williams, with a New Introduction by John Egerton (1988)-Manuscript (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Dishes and Beverages of the Old South-Planning and Outlines (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Dishes and Beverages of the Old South-Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Dishes and Beverages of the Old South-Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Dishes and Beverages of the Old South-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Dishes and Beverages of the Old South-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Dishes and Beverages of the Old South-Publication Materials-Contracts (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Dishes and Beverages of the Old South-Reviews (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Southern Magazine (1987-1988)-Background (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Drinking (Southern Magazine, January 1987)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Let Them Eat Cornbread (Southern Magazine, April 1987)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Book Collecting (Southern Magazine, May 1987)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Ice and Tea (Southern Magazine, July 1987)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Home Style Eateries (Southern Magazine, September 1987)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Turkey Calls (Southern Magazine, November 1987)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Oh, Ye Nogs and Custards (Southern Magazine, December 1987)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Pot of Gold (Southern Magazine, March 1988)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Salvation on a Plate (Southern Magazine, April 1988)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - The Way of Red Rice (Southern Magazine, August 1988)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - The Morning Watch (Southern Magazine, September 1988)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Kentucky Inns (Southern Magazine)-Manuscript, Unpublished (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Pound Cake, St. Augustine (Southern Magazine)-Manuscripts, Unpublished (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Planning and Outlines (for Southern Magazine articles) (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Research and Background Materials (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence-Incoming (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Southpoint Magazine (1989)-Proposals (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Judi’s Lyceum, The Brotherhood, and Images Magazine (1989-1990) (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Side Orders: Small Helpings of Southern Cookery and Culture (1990)-Manuscript, Partial Copy of Proofs (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Side Orders-Planning and Outlines (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Side Orders-Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Side Orders-Correspondence-Incoming (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Side Orders-Publication Materials-Proposals for Contract Negotiations (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Side Orders- Reviews (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Side Orders-Promotional Materials (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Athens of the West? (Images of Nashville, Spring 1990)-Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Athens of the West? -Planning and Outlines (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Athens of the West? -Articles and Handwritten Notes (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Subject Files (1980s)
  - South of the Border (Dillon, South Carolina, 1987) (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Fate Thomas, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Alternate Roots, (Arts Issue, Winter, 1988) (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Radical Spots in Education, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Shades of Gray (1991)
  - Manuscript-Introduction; Race and Class in Higher Education (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript-West Virginia’s Battle of the Books; Alex Haley’s Tennessee Roots (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript-Trial of the Highlander Folk School; The King Coal Good Times Blues (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript-A Gentleman’s Fight in Prince Edward County, Virginia; Heritage of a Heavyweight (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript-Claude Pepper’s Last Crusade; Maurice Mays and the Knoxville Race Riot of 1919 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript-The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray; Morris Dees and the Southern Poverty Law Center (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript-Hammond Academy: A Rebel Yell, Fading; The Enigma of the South; Index (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Edited Manuscript-Introduction; Race and Class in Higher Education (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Edited Manuscript-West Virginia’s Battle of the Books; Alex Haley’s Tennessee Roots (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Edited Manuscript-The Trial of the Highlander Folk School; The King Coal Good Times Blues (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Edited Manuscript-A Gentleman’s Fight in Prince Edward County, Virginia; Heritage Of a Heavyweight (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Edited Manuscript-Claude Pepper’s Last Crusade; Maurice Mays and the Knoxville Race Riot, 1919 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Edited Manuscript-The Enduring Mystery of James Earl Ray; Morris Dees and the Southern Poverty Law Center (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Edited Manuscript-Hammond Academy: A Rebel Yell, Fading; The Enigma of the South; Index (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Shades of Gray (1991)
  - Planning and Outlines (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Research and Background Materials-Research Notes (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-Incoming (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Publication Materials (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Reviews (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Materials (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Videotape-Mornings on Five, Recorded 11/25/91; Broadcast 11/30/91 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    See Box 89 (Oversized Box) for Proofs for Shades of Gray
- Southern Oral History Project (The University of North Carolina, 1993)
  - Planning and Funding (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Transcripts of Taped Interviews with:
  - Harry Ashmore (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Daisy Bates (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Gould Beech (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Betty Carter (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - James P. Coleman (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - LeRoy Collins (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Virginius Dabney (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Daniel Drake (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Durr (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Bill Emerson (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - John A. Griffin (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - William Gordon (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Harold Fleming (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - John Hope Franklin (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Grace Hamilton (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Alexander Heard (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Southern Oral History Project (The University of North Carolina, 1993)
  - John Ivey (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Guy B. Johnson (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Lyman Johnson (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Charles Jones (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Stetson Kennedy (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Calvin Kytle (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Hylan Lewis (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Sid McMath (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - John Popham (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Edgar Ray (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Modjesha Simpkins (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - George Stoney (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Herman Talmadge (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Margaret Walker (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - C. Vann Woodward (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Wilson Wyatt (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Transcripts of Taped Interviews with Wilma Dykeman and Ellis Arnall who denied (Box 69, Folder 17)
    Permission to add their tapes to the project
  - Correspondence-Outgoing (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence-Incoming (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Tapes, Southern Oral History Project (The University of North Carolina, 1993)
  Box of 31 Tapes (See transcripts above; typed list of tapes is in the box)
- Speak Now Against the Day (1994)
  - Manuscript (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Edited Typescript-Introduction; Prologue (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Edited Typescript-Part I, Chapters 1-3 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Edited Typescript-Part I, Chapters 4-5 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Edited Typescript-Part I, Chapters 6-7 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Edited Typescript-Part I, Chapters 8-10 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Edited Typescript-Part I, Chapters 11-12 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Edited Typescript-Part II, Chapters 1-2 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Edited Typescript-Part II, Chapters 3-5 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - EditedTypescript-Part II, Chapters 6-7 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Speak Now Against the Day (1994)
  - Edited Typescript-Part II, Chapter 8; Interlogue (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Edited Typescript-Part III, Chapters 1-2 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Edited Typescript-Part III, Chapters 3-4 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Edited Typescript-Part III, Chapters 5-7 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Edited Typescript-Part III, Chapters 8-9 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Edited Typescript-Part III, Chapters 10-11 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Edited Typescript-Part IV, Chapters 1-2 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Edited Typescript-Part IV, Chapters 3-4 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Edited Typescript-Epilogue (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Edited Typescript-Sources; Resources; Credits; Notes on Structure (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Edited Typescript-Captions (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Edited Typescript-Annotated Bibliography (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Edited Manuscript-Three and one-half inch computer disks (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Speak Now Against the Day (1994)
  - Planning and Outlines (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Research and Background Materials-Interviews (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Research and Background Materials-Handwritten Notes (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Research and Background Materials-Articles (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Speak Now Against the Day (1994)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 1-5- Handwritten Notes (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 1-5-Articles (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 1-5-Articles (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 6-7-Handwritten Notes (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 6-7-Articles (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 8-10-Handwritten Notes (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 8-10-Articles (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 8-10-Articles (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 8-10-Articles (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Speak Now Against the Day (1994)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 11-12-Handwritten Notes (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 11-12-Articles (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 11-12-Articles (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part I, Chapters 11-12-Newspaper Articles (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapter 1-Handwritten Notes 6, Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapter 1-Articles (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapter 2-Handwritten Notes (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapter 2-Articles (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapter 3-Handwritten Notes (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapter 3-Articles (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapters 4-5-Handwritten Notes (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapters 4-5-Handwritten Notes (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapters 4-5-Articles (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapters 4-5- Articles (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Speak Now Against the Day (1994)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapter 6-Handwritten Notes (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Research and Background Materials-Part II, Chapter 6-Articles (Box 76, Folder 2)